Hello, this is EYA on EYA censored
supernatural Bible changes on YouTube
and today is April 11th, 2026. I'm going
to be on a roll. I'm going to start
doing more videos like I did when I
first started my channel 10 years ago.
It was another channel, but you know
what I'm you know what I'm talking
about. I want to go ahead and talk about
some words that are in the Bible and
what they mean today.
The word pervert.
This is the definition for pervert.
Okay, I went ahead and I I looked it up
on Yahoo and this is what it says.
Alter something from its original
course, meaning, or state to a
distortion or corruption of what was
first intended. He was charged with
conspiring to pervert the course of
justice. And then when I click here, it
says a person whose sexual behavior is
regarded as abnormal and unacceptable.
[clears throat]
More definitions and word origins.
Late Middle English
um goes back to the late 19th century.
And there you have it. Then here's a
definition from Merriam-Webster
and it says um to cause to turn aside or
away from what is good or true or
morally right,
to divert to a wrong end or purpose, to
twist the meaning, to misinterpret.
Sorry about that.
One that has been perverted. One given
to some form of sexual perversion. Sorry
about that. I don't know why that just
popped up here.
So, there you have it. The definition of
pervert.
Well, I'm going to go ahead and show you
for those of you who don't know, again,
I've been covering these changes for the
past 10 years on YouTube and I have a
website called bible-changes.com
and you can find it Oops, sorry about
that. Let me just go here.
So, here is my website and you can click
on the search KJV index changes. I
created this as a great tool for those
of you who are interested in
finding Bible changes that are really
specific, okay? I have over 7,000 verses
that have been gathered that
show what's happened to scripture.
It's not every single change. Okay, that
would really be kind of impossible to
do.
But I want to go ahead and show you
this.
So, um let me just go ahead and do this.
So, now in the Bible, we have the word
pervert,
perverted, perverteth, perverting now in
the Bible in 21 verses.
And
you can just read these and you can see
how strange they are.
I'll go ahead and I'll read a few of
them to you. Like this one, Job 8:3.
Now, when you look at these Bible
changes on this index that I've created,
I'm going to remind you that just
because a word is highlighted doesn't
mean it's the only change in that verse,
okay? It means that particular word is
highlighted that we're looking for,
but oftentimes,
you'll see a verse has multiple changes
in it, grammar errors, punctuation
errors, um spelling errors, new words.
Even the verse that you remembered no
longer exists. You'll find new people
and modern words and words omitted,
doctrinal changes, literally nonsense
verses. But let me show you this one.
Job 8:3 says this today in the King
James Bible.
Doth God pervert judgment?
Or doth the Almighty pervert justice? As
if the Almighty
and God
are distinctly different.
Again,
let me read this again. Doth God pervert
judgment?
Or doth the Almighty pervert justice?
Well, first of all, you can see there's
something terribly wrong because there's
a question mark and then a small O.
So, that's an example and we know that
the Bible changes are changing the the
nature and character of God because why
is this happening? Because the God that
is now being portrayed in scripture
is that of the Antichrist, the impostor.
It's the abomination of desolation
standing in the holy place.
Now, here's another one. In Deuteronomy
27:19, it now says, "Cursed be he that
perverteth the judgment of the stranger,
fatherless, and widow, and all the
people shall say amen." It never said
that. It never said this quote right
here, "And all the people shall say
amen."
That's ridiculous, but not to mention
this language has been changed. These
are perversions. Now, let me go ahead
and show you some other ones here.
And then here in Job 34:12, it says,
"Yay! Yippee!
Woo!
Yahoo!" Lots of yays in the Bible. We
have yay-yays and nay-nays now in the
Bible. I kid you not, literally.
Yay-yays and nay-nays.
Lots of filler words now dropping in
scripture because they're taking away
real words
and dropping in filler words like hither
and thither and notwithstanding and
wheresoever and whereso
words that or whoso
words that mean nothing.
Filler words, okay? But now, let me go
ahead and read this again. "Yay!" In Job
34:12, "Yay! Yippee! Surely God will not
do wickedly, neither will the Almighty
pervert judgment."
Now, moving along. Now, hear me when I
say this. I loved reading scripture. I
I've been a Christian for decades and
I've never fallen away.
I I've been walking with Jesus for a
long time, years, decades.
And I loved reading scripture. I loved
reading scripture. I love my Father in
heaven
and I know his voice. And there are
foreign word invaders dropped into
scripture right now deliberately to
deceive the believer.
And this is what's causing the great
falling away happening right now, right
as we speak.
The abomination of desolation is
standing in the holy place and he who
has
he he who reads, let him understand and
I'm reading and I understand and I see
and I know.
Let me continue on.
A wicked man taketh a gift out of the
bosom to pervert the way of judgment.
And it goes on and on about perverting
judgment. Well, I'm going to scroll down
here, just stay with me.
I'm going to scroll down here.
And here it is right here, Jeremiah
23:26, "And the burden of the Lord shall
you mention no more, for every man's
word shall be his burden, for ye have
perverted the words of the living God."
This is exactly what's happened right
now. The words
of the living God are being perverted.
They're They're They're putting in
spells, okay, into scripture.
And we've talked about over the years
how the changes in scripture are
manifesting in reality, okay? Let me go
ahead and continue on here. There's so
much I can cover about this. But here's
another verse I'm going to read to you
and you can obviously see the changes.
Luke 23:2, "And they began to accuse him
saying, 'We found this fellow'" That's
right. "We found this fellow
perverting the nation
and forbidding to give tribute to Caesar
saying that he himself is Christ a
king."
This is supposedly about Jesus, the King
of kings and Lord of lords. And they're
saying that he is a fellow
perverting the nation. And I just read
to you the definition of
what it means
and I'm going to scroll up here. A
person whose sexual behavior is regarded
as abnormal and unacceptable.
And then you can see other changes that
are here, okay? You don't have to look
very far, but even this, Christ a king.
Because throughout scripture now, when
you're when you look at scriptures
related to Jesus,
they are changing
in scripture
the reality of God's
character
and his titles.
Now, keep in mind the the supremacy of
God,
the
the the the the reality of God being the
ultimate God is a non-negotiable. No
matter what happens to scripture.
The Bible does not
the Bible is not required
to prove the existence of God, okay? You
have to think through this.
Our faith doesn't rest in a book.
My faith rests in Jesus Christ, the King
of kings and Lord of lords.
One can be illiterate.
One can never have read scripture and
still know Jesus Christ as Lord and
Savior.
Okay?
But for
many, many years, the church has been
bowing their knee to the Bible, to a
book.
And so, what has Satan done? He's come
along and he's perverted scripture
through black magic.
Now, I know that it's not it's not from
only the publishers
because the Bibles [clears throat] that
we've owned for years and years
are satanically changing.
Those in museums and bookstores, but now
publishers are culpable because they're
printing the corrupted verses.
And meanwhile, church pastors are
silent.
Christian universities are silent.
Christian leaders are woefully silent.
And now they're teaching the corrupted
verses as if they're true.
Like that they would saying that Christ
was aching and is claiming that he he
was a fellow perverting the nation in
Luke 23:2.
I have to continue on here, but I want
to show you this one.
Um
But the point pervert the gospel of
Christ. This is what they're doing.
They're perverting the gospel of Christ.
And the Bible is filled with really
foul language. I'm going to go ahead and
share another verse with you. Give me a
minute.
There it is. I'm going to bring up the
new word infants in the Bible and I'm
going to show you this one. This is
Jesus in Luke 18:15. Now, keep in mind
when I say that, it really isn't the
Jesus that we know.
It's the Antichrist who's pretending
that he's the Lord in scripture.
But in Luke 18:15, this is what it says
now, and they brought unto him also
infants
that he would touch them.
But when his disciples saw it, they
rebuked them.
Yeah, so now Jesus, instead of blessing
the children,
he's now touching infants and being
rebuked by his disciples.
It's incredibly offensive.
And there are other ones. Like I'm
thinking of
um
there is a a scripture verse
where we all know the story of Jesus
washing the feet. Let me see if I can
find it. Oh, I don't think it's here.
Uh what I can do is I can go ahead and
probably pull it up.
Actually, I'm just going to go and
explain it to you and you can look it
up.
Do you remember the story? Of course you
do. Of Jesus washing the disciples'
feet.
Well, now when you go to read it,
it now says that Jesus had a towel
wrapped around him.
Right? He's a towel wrapped around him,
but then he takes it off
to to wash the disciples' feet.
Yeah, so basically he's walking around
naked.
These are just a couple of the changes
that are in scripture that are painting
Jesus Christ as being lewd,
of being a pervert.
And now we have words like pervert,
perverted, perverting in scripture. And
also
that name pervert is now being given to
him in scripture.
It's total blasphemy.
If this is the first time that you're
learning about these satanic changes to
scripture, I understand it could be
really difficult. I understand.
But
I'm glad that you're here.
And we've been praying for you.
And I pray that every person in this
community will stay strong.
Be uncompromising.
Keep your eyes on Jesus.
But do not weary. Do not grow weary. We
must not grow weary. We need to be
filled with the Holy Spirit.
We need to have our eyes set on Jesus.
And be completely submitted and yielded
to his lordship.
Preach the gospel. The good news is
found in Jesus Christ. And warn everyone
as well
that the Bible is satanically changing.
We cannot shout this enough.
Let us be vocal.
Let us be Let us be courageous in this
hour.
And you know, I wonder
I'm wondering a lot of things right now,
especially as we're
it really feels like we're coming up to
the finishing line.
And
there's such limited time.
And I've been speaking of that for the
past 10 years.
And my goodness,
have the times been wild.
It's been absolutely wild.
So, with that said, you guys be strong
and courageous. Do not fear be dismayed
for the Lord your God is with you
wherever you go. Until next time.